

CONTACT

- nunnapat_ch@yahoo.com
- (786)8048936
- 🏠 Miami, FL
- https://github.com/nunn a19
- https://www.linkedin.co
 m/in/nunnapat/

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript, Express.js, MongoDB, Node.js, HTML, CSS, SCSS, jQuery, Bootstrap.

PROJECT

The Meteor Game

the meteor fall from the sky in the city and you need to save the city by move missile to crash the meteor Technologies Used: JavaScript, Git, Canvas, HTML5, CSS

NaNaWix

Technologies Used: JavaScript, Node.JS, MongoDB, Mongoose, Express, PassportJS, HTML, SASS, Bootstrap, Heroku

NUNNAPAT CHIRALERDSITTHIKHUN

ABOUT

Currently studying at Ironhack's Web Development bootcamp in Miami, FL. I have been living here in Miami for 6 years now working as a chef de cuisine, sushi chef and kitchen manager. After working for a few years I felt the desire to change career and learn something new. While searching for possibilities I noticed how attracted to coding I was and so a great school had to naturally be part of the plan. My goal is to keep learning software engineering until I can become a great asset/associate to a reputable company.

EXPERIENCE

Kitchen Manager | YuGo sushi burritos, Miami FL | Mar 2015 - Feb 2017

- responsibility inventory every month and in charge ordering product every day.
- In charge of 12employees schedule, In charge training the employees,
- responsible HR, Control & management system in the kitchen.

Head Sushi Chef | Lee Sushi, Miami FL | Mar 2014 - Mar 2015

- responsibility check the stock in the restaurant,
- prepare & cook the food follow by order .

Sushi chef/Line Cook | Tokyo blue restaurant, Miami FL| Jun 2013 - Feb 2014

- responsibility prepare the food.
- responsibility line salad and desert

Apprentice | Grand Hyatt Erawan Bangkok, Thailand | Nov 2012 - Feb 2013

• responsibility prepare the food for buffet & catering.in the hotel.

EDUCATION

Ironhack bootcamp, Miami, FL | Jan 22th 2019 - Mar 30th 2019

Web Development

Activities and Societies: Ironhack is an immersive bootcamp with locations all over the globe, offering 9-week courses in Full Stack Web Development and UX/UI Design. (400+ hours) - Technologies: JavaScript, React.js, Node.js, Express, MongoDB, HTML and CSS.

Dusit Thani College, Thailand | 2009 - 2013

Bachelor's degree Kitchen and Restaurant Management

Nakhonpathom Municipality Vocational College, Thailand | 2005 - 2008

Deploma

Food and Nutrition Program